YYeTs.com
人人影视
*Better pray for hell*
时间轴： 浓子   萌    校对： 苏小黛   胖兔纯
Good morning, reverend.
早上好  牧师
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Join me?
一起吃吗
There are no words
您对我丈夫的
to encompass my overwhelming gratitude
再造之恩
at your reclamation of my husband.
我的感激无以言表
When I think what might have transpired
如果不是您去到了那儿
- had you not been there... - Indeed?
-后果真不堪想象  -是吗
Exactly what might have transpired?
会有什么后果你说说看
- Excuse me? - well...
-什么  -我是说...
Would not your slave girl simply have taken him on to hospital?
你家女仆难道不会直接送他去医院吗
Yes.
当然
Yes, it was you who sent her to his rescue,
正是  是你派了她去救他
was it not?
不是吗
Once I'd heard of the accident.
我一收到消息就立马派她去了
I am perplexed, though.
不过  我很困惑
Tell me, why was George scurried off with such haste and secrecy?
为什么这么着急秘密地把乔治送出去
He goes often to Boston.
他经常去波士顿
- His illness. - He's not ill.
-去看病  -他没病
- He's spelled. - No.
-他是被下咒了  -不
That's impossible.
怎么可能
Consider...
你想想...
has not George suffered this mysterious malady
乔治是不是无缘无故
without explication for several years now,
就被这怪病缠了好几年
and have not the doctors expressed utter befuddlement
而且  是不是没有医生能说出
as to its cause?
这到底是何原因
- Yes, but... - Yes. In such cases,
-是的  但...  -那么在那种情况下
The answer is oft the simplest one.
答案就再简单不过了
George is not ill.
他根本没病
He is under the influence of the devil's darkest tool --
而是受制于恶魔的邪恶爪牙
a witch's spell.
也就是巫师的咒语
And it is quite likely that this speller resides close at hearth.
而且似乎这个施咒者与之非常亲近
No.
不
Perhaps even in the hallowed halls of your own home.
也许就住在你家
Say it.
有话就说吧
Say what?
说什么
The accusation.
你不是想控告我吗
It dances on your tongue.
你憋了很久了吧
Well, I assure you, you are mistaken.
你误会我的意思了
Then I wish to bring my husband home immediately.
我想即刻把我丈夫接回去
I think not, Mrs. Sibley.
恕难从命  西布里夫人
You would deny me that right?
你凭什么拒绝我
I must deny you that right
我必须拒绝你
until we can discover the origin of the spell.
直到我们发现咒语的根源
Then I would ask, or, rather, insist,
那我请求...  不  我要求
that someone attend to Mr. Sibley.
找个人照顾西布里先生
Someone who has experience with his travails.
最好是有照顾他经验的人
What about that young man...
那个年轻人怎么样
the one who was to take him to Boston, huh?
就是那个载他去波士顿的
- Isaac? - Ah.
-艾萨克  -恩
Isaac will do.
就他吧
He sleeps still?
他还在昏睡中吗
Under the care of sentries.
有侍卫看守着呢
Oh, and, Mary.
对了  玛丽
Be of good heart.
放心吧
Mr. Lamb, the barkeep, tells me that he may wake at any moment.
酒吧老板兰布先生说他可能随时醒来
Cotton.
柯顿
No difference between me and those that already rest.
我跟那些死人没什么分别
Besides a still-beating heart
只是我的心还跳动在
in a shell where my soul no longer resides.
一具灵魂空洞的躯壳里
Oh, boy.
天啊
Good morning, reverend.
早啊  牧师
I wonder --
我在想...
what would it take to get you to your feet?
怎样才能让你起身
Why would you wish to?
你为什么想这么做
I fear I may have...
我担心自己可能...
judged you too harshly, Reverend Mather.
对你太刻薄了  麦哲牧师
It is only now, when leaving my childhood behind,
只是现在  当童年远去
that I realize we are, past and forever,
我才意识到  无论过去还是以后
our fathers' children.
我们都是为人子女
And we can no more control who they be
我们不能选择他们是谁
and how they came to form us
他们怎样塑造我们
then we can the rise and setting of the sun.
但是我们能做回自己
I am sorry about your girl.
你爱的那个姑娘  我很遗憾
Thank you.
谢谢你
May we see you home?
我们送你回家好吗
Come on.
起来
Once he's settled, Captain,
把他送回家安置好后  上尉
may I ask a favor of you?
你能帮我个忙吗
Surely.
当然
"I think not, Mrs. Sibley."
"恕难从命  西布里夫人"
As if he were Socrates and I, a student at his knee.
就好像他是苏格拉底  我是跪在他跟前的学生
Let me kill him, please.
让我去杀了他吧
No.
不行
Let me ease this burden for you, as I've done the others.
让我帮你减轻这个负担  就跟处理其他人一样
Increase Mather is known throughout the world,
不论在新世界还是旧世界
new and old.
英克里斯·麦哲都声名远扬
His disappearance or death will not be taken lightly.
他消失或者死亡肯定会引起不小的轰动
His head will sit on no man's platter.
不能平白无故就让他死去
He's no match for you, certainly.
他自然无法与你相提并论
That is where you are wrong, child.
这样想你就错了  孩子
This is our truest test
这是对我们的真实考验
to battle equals.
去与势均力敌之人战斗
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Reverend.
牧师
Mercy.
梅西
Hello.
您好
I wonder if I might have a private word
我能否跟我女儿
with my daughter.
单独说几句话
I think not, Reverend.
恕难从命  牧师
- I - Fetch me Isaac.
-我...  -去帮我把艾萨克找来
Now.
马上
I am, um...
我...
astounded at the charity you've shown my child,
没想到您对我的孩子如此仁慈宽厚
but if I wish to see her,
但如果我想见她
is that not a father's right?
这不是一个父亲应有的权利吗
Why, in particular, do you wish to see her, Reverend?
你为什么想见她呢  牧师
Were you perhaps considering another exorcism?
你是想对她用其他驱邪方法吗
Do your days grow dull,
身边没有孩子
lacking a child to beat and torture
让你打骂折磨是不是很无聊
and the nights far too lonely with no daughter to visit?
漫漫长夜没有女儿陪伴是不是很孤单
- I would never - Mercy is mine.
-我绝不会...  -梅西是我的人
Return here again and these accusations will be made public.
你再来的话我就公开指责你了
What of master Sibley? Has he woken?
西布里先生怎么样了  醒了吗
The elders will wait no longer.
长老们不想再等了
They require an audience with you today.
他们要求今天与你见面
Has he woken?
他醒了吗
Any moment now.
随时都可能醒
It were an accident, ma'am.
那是意外  夫人
A wayward timber in the path,
一根黑松木挡在路中间
and we found ourselves at sixes and sevens.
然后我们就都跌下马车不省人事了
It's okay, Isaac.
没事  艾萨克
I know you've done your best.
我知道你已经尽力了
The reverend summons me now,
牧师现在找我
heaven knows why, but I fear each second he's made to wait --
不知道为什么  但我担心他是想等...
He will ask you to watch over Mr. Sibley.
他会让你照顾西布里先生
- He will? - At my grave insistence,
-是吗  -在我的强烈坚持下
since he refuses my desire
因为他拒绝让我
to bring my husband home to proper care.
把我丈夫带回家照料
He refuses you?
他拒绝你
Salem reels out of control like an unwieldy spin top
塞勒姆就像一个笨重的陀螺一样转失控了
at the whim of Increase Mather.
都是因为英克里斯·麦哲的随心所欲
A tonic... the pain and ease of sleep.
这是减轻痛苦有助于睡眠的药剂
Isaac, I beseech you,
艾萨克  我请求你
in this most private and important matter,
这是一件极其重要而又私人的事
do my bidding where I cannot.
帮我一下吧
Oh, uh...
这个...
Dose him immediately and keep him so.
马上让他服下  并且药不能停
George should not be made to suffer
不该让乔治遭受
for Mather senior's unfounded suspicions.
老麦哲毫无根据的怀疑
H-he shall not.
不会的
And Isaac...
艾萨克...
Between us.
此事你知我知
Like so many of Salem's secrets.
就像塞勒姆的很多其他秘密一样
Are you aware, son?
你知道吗  孩子
Your story is known far and wide throughout the land.
你的故事真是无人不知无人不晓
Isaac the fornicator.
私通者艾萨克
No, no, no. Do not bow your head in shame.
不不不  不要因羞愧而低下头
Head up. Get your head up.
抬起头来  抬起来
Head up. Head up.
抬头  抬头
The story of Isaac the fornicator
私通者艾萨克的故事
is a holy one.
是神圣的
It is used as a living precedent by we puritans
它被我们清教徒当做一个活生生的例子
to illustrate to the children the evils of lust.
用来向孩子们说明欲望的罪恶
No, no. Your sin and your suffering...
不不  你的罪恶和痛苦...
It has been transformed into a great and a holy blessing.
已经被转化为神圣而伟大的祝福了
For, my son...
因为  孩子...
You felt the hand of God.
你感受到了上帝之手
He's touched you.
他碰触了你
He's working through you.
他是在考验你
He's chosen you.
他选择了你
No.
不
How many can say that they have been chosen by God?
有几个人能说自己是被上帝选中的啊
Chosen for what?
选我干什么
Son, have you ever imagined a world beyond Salem?
孩子  你想过塞勒姆以外的生活吗
- I... - Get your head up, your head up,
-我  -头抬起来  抬起来
Your head up, your head up.
抬头  抬头
I have a good life here, sir.
我在这里生活得很好  先生
Yes, performing meager errands for Mrs. Sibley.
是啊  你在这里给西布里夫人跑腿
She's been good to me. Always.
她待我很好  一直很好
Her charity binds you to her bidding.
她对你的施舍让你对她言听计从
No. No, no, no, Isaac.
不  不不不   艾萨克
Out there.
外面
Out there, boy!
外面  孩子
There's a vast world out there,
外面是大千世界
full of... full of opportunities,
机会  机会遍地都是
and if you... if you would walk the straight road
如果你  如果你想在阳光下抬头挺胸
in the sunlight with your head up,
走上康庄大道
I would take you with me to see it.
我会带你出去亲眼看看
I would.
我会的
Would you like that?
你觉得怎么样
What would I have to do?
那我需要怎么做
Well...
这个...
You will have to --
你得...
Have to tend to Mr. Sibley there.
你得来照顾西布里先生
...make certain that he is fresh and tidy,
保证他每天整洁如新
and that is no easy task, hmm?
这可不是件容易的事
Most importantly, you must alert me the moment that he wakes.
最重要的是  他醒时你必须通知我
Yes.
没错
Can you do that, hmm?
你能做到吗
Do you mind me asking, sir,
恕我冒昧问一句  先生
What these are for?
这些是用来做什么的
Protection for Mr. Sibley against...
用来保护西布里先生免受
outer forces.
外界势力危害
It's cremated ash...
这是骨灰
...of a 200-year-old witch.
一名两百岁女巫的骨灰
And, Isaac...
对了  艾萨克
I burned her myself.
她是我亲手烧死的
So, the roof needs patching there and there,
屋顶有两处需要修补
A fresh coat of paint wouldn't hurt,
墙面也最好能重新油漆一下
nor would four or five more beds for the smaller children,
另外我们还需要四五张床来安置小一点的孩子
And... I'm overwhelming you.
还有  我是不是吓到你了
No, no.
不  不
I'm eager to put my energies to good.
我很乐意能将精力花在做善事上
Exactly.
我也正是这么想的
The children are frightened, captain.
孩子们都被吓坏了  上尉
Another hung today and not an inkling who's to be next.
今天又有一个人被绞死  也不知道谁会是下一个
They're unsure who to fear more...
如今他们也不知道谁更可怕
Witches or those who pursue them.
巫师  还是追捕他们的那些人
Well, who can blame them?
谁能怪他们呢
He doesn't play with the others.
他不怎么合群
The dark-haired boy.
那个深色头发的男孩
He's been here two years.
他来这两年了
His parents were murdered by Indians.
父母都被印第安人杀害
They say he saw.
有人说他目睹了一切
No one knows how he survived.
没人知道他是怎么活下来的
Has anyone asked?
有人问过他吗
He doesn't talk.
他从不说话
At least, not anymore.
至少  从那以后
Not since...then.
就再也不说了
Excuse me.
打扰一下
Do you know anything about patching a roof?
你会修屋顶吗
Mrs. Sibley?
西布里夫人
The mistress is out.
女主人出去了
Anything needed to be said to her can be said to me.
有什么要告诉她的  都可以对我说
Oh, that's beautiful!
它真漂亮
My familiar.
我的亲信
Familiar?
亲信
A gift from the devil to do my bidding,
这是恶魔的馈赠  它为我卖命
My spiritual companion.
我的灵魂伴侣
This is how she feeds.
我是这样喂食它的
Will I get a familiar?
我也能得到亲信吗
In time.
会有的
How do I choose?
我要如何选择它呢
You don't.
由不得你
It chooses you.
它会选择你
Good day, Mrs. Sibley.
日安  西布里夫人
Girls.
姑娘们
We're off to meet mercy in the graveyard.
我们正准备去墓地与梅西见面
Well.
这样吗
On your way, then.
那就快去吧
We all grieve the loss of our sister.
姐妹的死我与你们一样深感悲痛
I do not argue this.
我不会为自己辩白
But beg remembrance that I was given little choice.
但我想让你们知道  我别无选择
The malum...
恶灵
...without which our grand rite would not be possible.
我们大祭典的必须之物
Rose brought it here, this instrument of death,
萝丝未经我同意  便将这件死亡之器
without my knowledge, to challenge and defeat me.
带来了这里  想以此挑战并击败我
It is for you, retrieved at great cost,
为了你们  也为了我们崇高的大业
relinquished with love and ardor for our cause.
我不惜一切代价将其夺回
I leave you now with the only tool
如今  我将它交予你们
that exists on earth to control me.
这个世界上唯一能控制我的物品
The trick to making shakes is to split them...
劈柴的诀窍在于让它们自然裂开
Not chopped or sawed, but to split.
不靠砍也不靠锯  而是裂开
Thank you.
谢谢
Your turn.
到你了
Right! Well done.
就是这样  干得漂亮
Captain.
上尉
Mrs. Sibley.
西布里夫人
Young man.
年轻人
Why don't you go see if there's any fresh water.
你能去给我找些水来喝吗
Big doings this morning.
今早的事真是轰动
Seems every day brings its fair share of surprises.
如今每天似乎都有意想不到的事情发生
I heard old Increase took possession of your husband.
我听说你丈夫在英克里斯那里
Yes, he did.
是的
And I'm eager to get him back.
我想把他带回来
You are?
是吗
Why?
为什么
Is it so unusual, captain,
一个妻子想让丈夫回家
for a wife to want her husband at home?
就这么让人惊讶吗  上尉
In most cases, it's not unusual at all.
对大部分人来说不是
I heard my hard worker was thirsty.
听说我的帮手口渴了
Oh, Mrs. Sibley.
您也在啊  西布里夫人
Uh, fresh apple water on offer.
要来点新鲜的苹果汁吗
No, thank you, Anne.
不了  谢谢你  安
Good day, captain.
再见  上尉
Young man.
年轻人
Captain.
上尉
May I?
这个能给我吗
If you're going to capitulate to your weakness,
就算你已经决定了彻底放纵自我
must it be on constant public display?
你一定要弄得这么众人皆知吗
Shall I leave public display to you, father?
或许我该将舞台留给您  父亲
Shall we abolish the noose
不如把绞刑架拆了
so that you may break necks with your own two hands?
这样您就能亲手折断他们的脖子
She was dead.
她之前就死了
The whore runner killed herself.
那个鸨母是自杀的
She was already dead,
她都已经死了
and yet you hung her.
而你还要绞死她
I said she would hang.
我说过她会被绞死
and hang she did.
我说到做到
We are nothing if we do not keep our word,
如果言而无信  那我们就什么都不是
A principle which seems to mean very little to you, I fear.
可惜你却似乎并不懂得这条原则
Must you hate me so?
您就这么憎恨我吗
Oh, Cotton.
我的柯顿
Your mother was a Cotton, as you know.
你母亲是柯顿家族一员
And my stepsister.
也是我同母异父的妹妹
Our marriage was a historical inevitability.
我们的婚姻是历史的必然
The Cottons and the Mathers...
柯顿家和麦哲家
Who could resist such a..
谁能拒绝两家
Such a joining of...of power and prestige?
如此的强强联合呢
Certainly not you.
你当然不会拒绝
She was a good woman,
她是个好女人
and she was a fit enough mother,
也是个称职的母亲
But...
但是
I didn't love her.
我并不爱她
I didn't love.
我不懂爱
And then you were born.
后来  便有了你
And there you were, a...
然后你出生了
Squalling mess of limbs and of hair, and...
这么小的一个小人儿  只会哭
You weren't much.
这么微不足道
But you were enough to show me love.
但你却足以让我明白了爱
What utter irony
真是讽刺
That you would then take the self-same thing from me.
如今你却执意要夺走我身边的爱
You are cut off, sir!
你不能再喝了  先生
No. I have money!
不  我有钱
I will drink muchly and often!
我要喝个痛快
You will not. Now be on your way.
不行  赶紧离开
I think not.
我不干
Oh, no, no. Whoa. Go!
不行  走开
The wine is from god.
美酒是上帝的赏赐
The drunkard is from the devil.
醉汉则是魔鬼的惩罚
Pull yourself together.
赶紧振作起来
There's much work to be done.
还有很多事要做
Let me kill him.
让我杀了他
I have told you.
我告诉过你了
We cannot kill Increase.
不能杀了英克里斯
Not silly old Increase.
不是又老又蠢的英克里斯
Mr. Sibley.
我是说西布里先生
This is what you teach her?
你就是这么教她的吗
For any problem, murder is the first course of action?
遇到问题  首先就想到杀人
We cannot kill George.
我们不能杀了乔治
Why not?
为什么
You are so powerful... you alone.
你如此有权势  你大权在握
You do not need him.
你不需要他
That is where you are wrong, my dear.
这你就错了  亲爱的
We need him desperately.
我们非常需要他
Without george, it all goes away.
没有乔治  一切就都没了
I am a widow with nothing...
我就只是个一无所有的寡妇
No business to run, no voice with the selectmen.
无权掌控生意  无权在委员会中发声
With him alive, I can speak through him...
只要他活着  我就能通过他来发话
A puppet to parrot his wishes and thoughts.
做一个模仿他意愿的玩偶
But dead, he is useless and I am without power.
但他死了就没用了  我也就没有权势了
But how will you stop him from speaking?
可你要如何阻止他说出实情
I will enter his mind and destroy it from within.
我要进入他的大脑  从内部毁了他
His body will live on, but his mind will be gone.
他的肉身还活着  但不会再有意识了
How will you do that?
这要怎么做
Quiet girl! That is enough questions.
闭嘴  问题够多了
Don't you tell me to be quiet.
你无权让我闭嘴
- Quiet.  - Enough!
-闭嘴  -够了
Both of you, leave me now.
你们俩都出去
- But I can help you.  - Get out!
-可我能帮你  -出去
Let go of me!
放开我
Let go!
放开
You know who we could kill?
知道我们能杀了谁吗
You.
你
You can't. She would never let you.
不行  她不会让你这么做的
Maybe, maybe not.
也许不会  也许会
You don't want to find out.
你不会想知道的
You're jealous and spiteful and awful.
你这个嫉妒刻薄的坏女人
Years... I have waited many, many years.
我已经等很多很多年了
Stay out of my way, you little bitch.
别碍我的事  贱人
Mrs. Sibley's only ever had your best interest at heart.
西布里夫人一心只为你好
Yet still...
可尽管如此
Your moment's worst desperation,
在你最为绝望的时刻
It was not her name you uttered for rescue
开口求救却并未说出她的名字
But that of the reverend Mather senior.
你居然叫了老麦哲牧师
What do I,
我这个
Who have known only violence
在你那里只得到过暴力
and malice from your eager hands,
和恶意的人
care a whit about your rosy outlook?
又怎么会在乎你的死活呢
Mary.
玛丽
Free of your precious familiar,
如今摆脱了你的亲信
I finally got hold of my dreams back.
我终于又赢回了梦想
Hmm. A beatific choice
在你这黑暗扭曲的意识里
For such a dark and twisted mind.
这还真是个美好的选择
You remember coming here?
你还记得来过这儿吗
Yes. A picnic.
记得  那次野餐
The one and only day I almost didn't despise you.
你唯一没让我心怀鄙视的一天
You never gave me a chance.
你从没给过我机会
Your mind was long made up.
你早就对我下了定论
Can you blame me?
能怪我吗
You stole my life.
你偷走了我的人生
And now you've stolen mine.
现在你则偷走了我的
We are close.
我们就快成功了
So very close.
非常接近了
The grand rite is almost complete.
大祭典就快完成了
And then what?
然后呢
Another kingdom for you to rule?
又一个王国供你主宰吗
Yes.
没错
A world in which I no longer need you.
一个我不再需要你的世界
A blessed world in which you can finally die.
在那个美好的世界里  你终于可以彻底死去
Peril and threats.
你就这么迫害威胁自己的丈夫吗
Many a union has relied on less.
比我们更不堪的夫妇数不胜数
Don't look so worried, George.
别这么担心  乔治
We're a little ways off yet.
我们还没有完全成功
For now, I just need you quiet,
如今  我只需要你闭嘴
Sleeping like an angel in your dirty bibs and nappies.
在你肮脏的围兜里像个天使般沉睡吧
Farewell, George.
永别了  乔治
You bitch!
贱人
Oh, that bastard.
混蛋
Sibley?
西布里吗
Increase Mather.
英克里斯·麦哲
He was there.
他在那里
Protecting george.
保护着乔治
Guarding his mind even in sleep.
即便是他睡梦中的意识
We have another problem.
我们还有个麻烦
We must do something about the girl.
我们必须对那女孩采取点措施
Mercy.
梅西
She is...unreliable.
她很不可靠
It is only a matter of time before
终有一天我们将无法再控制他
we can no longer control her.
这只是个时间问题
At a time such as this
此时此刻
when I am nearer to discovery and annihilation
我比任何时候都有可能被发现
than ever before,
命运悬于一线
you would distract yourself
你却让自己
with petty jealousy and spiteful accusations.
为那些不值一提的嫉妒和恶意中伤分心
I am trying to make --
我试着要
Never have I needed you more.
我比任何时候都需要你
And never have you disappointed me so gravely.
你却从没像如今这样让我失望
I would do anything for you.
我愿意为你做任何事
- I love you. - Oh, and I wish to god you didn't.
-我爱你  -我倒希望你别爱我
Love me less and you will love me better.
别那么爱我  或许这样会更好
Find a way to get to George.
想办法接近乔治
Tomorrow, we'll work on the paint.
明天我们涂漆
That is, if you're still available, of course.
当然了  如果你还有空的话
Excellent.
干得好
Excellent, son.
干得好  孩子
Stephen.
史蒂芬
You've seen my daughter.
你见过我女儿
You can move along. There's kids here.
你可以走了  这里只有孩子
I'm looking for a kid -- my kid.
我就是在找孩子  我的孩子
And I said, "Move along."
我说了  快滚
Mr. Hopkins.
霍普金斯先生
How can we help you?
有什么能帮你的吗
My daughter came to stay here after when I was in jail?
我入狱之后  我女儿是不是住在这里
Emily?
艾米莉
No, Mr. Hopkins. She did not.
不  霍普金斯先生  她没有
Have you seen her around?
你在附近见过她吗
No, sir. I haven't.
不  先生  我没有
You tell her I'm looking for her.
告诉她我在找她
You tell her she needs to come home.
告诉她  让她赶紧回家
Yes, Mr. Hopkins. I'll do that.
是  霍普金斯先生  我会的
Lizzy...
利兹
Did you bring the chicken feathers
你把鸡毛
and the dried horse dung?
和干马粪带来了吗
I brung the feathers, but the dung weren't dry.
鸡毛我带来了  但是马粪不太干
And what about the mice?
老鼠呢
They scattered when the cat come to the trap.
猫把陷阱里的老鼠都吓跑了
Mercy is to be here any minute.
梅西马上就要到了
Must I do everything myself?
难道什么事都要我亲自做吗
Miss Hopkins, may I have a word?
霍普金斯小姐  能借一步说话吗
Your father has been freed.
你父亲被释放了
I see.
知道了
And he's been looking for you,
他正在找你
asks that you come home immediately.
说让你马上回家
Miss Hale.
霍尔小姐
Can we help you?
有什么可以帮忙的吗
I've only come to tell Miss Hopkins
我只是来告诉霍普金斯小姐
that her father has been freed.
她父亲被释放了
How kind.
你人真好
And that he seemed...
他似乎
quite inebriated and not himself,
酩酊大醉失去理智了
and that perhaps she oughtn't to go home tonight.
也许她今晚最好先别回家
Perhaps she ought to stay in the orphanage
或许可以在孤儿院待一晚
where she'd be safe.
在那里她会很安全
She is safe.
她很安全
With us.
和我们在一起
Is she?
是吗
Would you care to stay and...
或许你可以留下
see for yourself...
亲眼见证
Anne?
安
Not tonight.
今晚不了
Stop.
住手
What is that?
那是什么
A tonic. For pain.
这是止痛药剂
Where did you get it?
你从哪里拿到的
Mr. Lamb gave it to me
兰姆先生给我的
- while you were out. - No.
-你出去的时候  -不是
No?
不是吗
Young man...
年轻人
Young man, I offered you an opportunity, did I not?
年轻人  我给过你机会不是吗
Do you remember?
你还记得
The world -- the vast world, the sunlight.
世界  广袤的世界  阳光
I somehow suspected you would find a way
我曾经怀疑过你
to undermine yourself.
还是会忍不住自轻自贱
But I did -- I hoped against hope that you wouldn't,
虽然我希望你不会这么做
but you did.
你却仍被我不幸言中
Because not only are you a cretin, you're a failure.
因为你不仅是个白痴还是个废物
You're a cretinous failure, and like all failures,
你是个无可救药的废物  和所有废物一样
You say to yourself, "But I never get the chance!
你对自己说  "我从未有过机会
I never get the opportunity,"
从未得到机遇"
But it just ain't so, is it?
但其实并不是这样  不是吗
No.
不
And like every failure, what do you do?
和所有废物一样  你做了什么
You just piss in the well of possibility.
你在机会面前退却了
And now you are going to tell me who gave you the potion.
现在你告诉我是谁给你这药剂的
Stiff as a stick, cold as a marble.
硬如干柴  冷如岩石
Light as a spirit, lift yourself.
轻如精灵  轻徙鸟举
Light as a feather, stiff as a board.
轻如羽毛  硬如石板
Master spider, stilted or stifled...
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Spin us a web and heed our call.
编汝之网  回吾之召
Who gave it you?
谁给你的
Head up. Head up.
抬头  抬头
- It's not a potion. - It's not a potion?
-它不是药剂  -不是药剂吗
It's not a po--
它不是
Look at me, boy.
看我  孩子
It's -- it's medicine.
这是  补药
One more time.
再说一次
I'm going to ask you, who gave it to you?
我问你  谁给你的
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Spin us a web and heed our call.
编汝之网  回吾之召
What we'll do is this --
我们会这么做
It's medicine.
这是补药
I'm going to slit your belly open.
我会把你的肚子剖开
I'm going to reach in, pull out,
我会伸手进去猛的一拉
and I'm going to throttle you with your own intestines.
然后用你的肠子勒住你的脖子
...heed our call.
回吾之召
Master spider, stilted or stifled,
蜘蛛之王  收放自若
Spin us a web and heed our call.
编汝之网  回吾之召
No. No. No.
不  不  不
Now, you tell me right now,
现在  你赶紧告诉我
who gave it to you?!
谁给你的
Tell me, Isaac!
告诉我  艾萨克
Tell me!
告诉我
Mrs. Sibley could bring no harm to a living thing.
西布里夫人绝不会伤害生灵
If -- if she provided me the medicine,
只要是她给的药水
that's good enough for me.
我绝对相信她
Mrs. Sibley, eh?
西布里夫人  是吗
Well done.
干得好
Off with you now.
你现在可以走了
Go.
走
Go on! Out of my sight!
快走  从我眼前消失
Isaac the fornicator!
私通者艾萨克
George.
乔治
Hello, father.
你好  父亲
Told you I'd get out.
跟你说了他们会放了我的
Yes, you did.
是的  你说了
I told you this weren't over.
我说过这事没完
You'll be sold still, if the whores will have you.
你依然会被卖掉  如果妓女还要你
I'm not going anywhere.
我哪都不去
You will.
你会的
You will go where I tell you!
你会去我要你去的地方
I won't.
我不会
I won't. I --
我不会  我
Please!
求你
Henry Hopkins.
亨利·霍普金斯
What is this?
这是干什么
Stephen.
史蒂芬
That's his name, the boy.
他叫这名字  那孩子
He told you?
他告诉你的吗
Yep.
是的
Two years without speaking,
两年了  他一言不发
and in one day, he tells you his name.
而你只用一天就知道了他的名字
He must have really taken to you, captain.
他一定很喜欢你  上尉
No, I wouldn't say that.
不  我不这么觉得
And who could blame him?
谁又能怪他
Boys need attention
男孩子总需要特别关注
and hard work to burn off their energy.
还有辛勤劳动来消耗他们多余的精力
And I'm grateful...
我很感激
for your hard work.
您的辛勤努力
It's the first hours passed since I've come back
这是我回来以后第一次
where I haven't thought about witches.
不再满脑子都想着巫师的事
I supposed one could choose that life --
我想人们都会愿意选择这种生活
Honest work, community, a loving family,
本分工作  团结互助  温馨的家庭
and not a witch in sight.
不会再有巫师
Maybe there's hope for us yet.
也许我们还有希望
You!
你
Alert the selectmen.
去通知行政委员
Another witch has been revealed. Follow me.
又一个女巫已经出现  跟我来
Or maybe not.
也许不是
Mary Sibley!
玛丽·西布里
Your husband is awake.
你丈夫醒了
George is awake?
乔治醒了
Has he spoken?
他说话了吗
He is rendered incapable of speech.
他已被夺取言语能力
Nevertheless, the name of his tormentor has been divulged.
然而  让他饱受折磨之人的姓名已出现
What does that mean --
那是什么意思
"Rendered unable to speak"?
被夺取言语能力
Do you recognize this potion?
你认得这瓶药剂吗
Yes.
是的
It's a physic for pain.
那是止痛药剂
I gave it to Isaac to give to Mr. Sibley.
我让艾萨克拿去给西布里先生的
A physic for pain?
止痛药剂
Tell me, would a physic for pain
告诉我  止痛药剂会不会
seal Mr. Sibley's mouth shut...
让西布里先生的嘴被
with a golden web?
黄金蛛网封住呢
A tonic for pain.
止痛药剂
Nothing more.
别无其他
Might I suggest, father,
我能说一句吗  父亲
That Mrs. Sibley's tonic is just that,
西布里夫人的药水可能如其所述
and the work of the web is due,
而造成蛛网出现的
more likely, to the real witch's spider familiar.
很可能是真正巫师的蜘蛛亲信
Yes.
是的
It's a possibility. Search the house.
是一种可能  搜查房屋
Wait!
等下
I'm sorry, sir.
我很抱歉  先生
Did you say a spider?
你是说蜘蛛吗
The Lewis child, once tortured and possessed by witches.
路易丝家的孩子  曾经被巫师附身折磨
Yet now she looks remarkably well.
可如今她看起来十分健康
All due to Mrs. Sibley's kindness.
多亏了西布里夫人的悉心照料
She saved my life.
她拯救了我的生命
I was tortured and tormented,
我曾被饱经折磨
at the verge of begging for death,
在死亡边缘寻求解脱
and Mary sibley delivered me from evil.
而玛丽·西布里将我带离邪恶
Which is why I hesitate to say --
所以我有些犹豫要不要说
What is it you have to say, girl?
你想要说什么  姑娘
The other morning,
那天早晨
when Mrs. Sibley was out on shipping business...
当西布里夫人外出处理船运业务的时候
- Yes? - ...I did pass Tituba's room,
-然后  -我经过了缇图芭的房间
and she was doing the strangest thing.
当时她正在做一件极其诡异的事
Tell us, Mercy. Tell us what you saw.
告诉我们  梅西  告诉我们你看到了什么
She held a spider to her neck.
她将一个蜘蛛捧在肩头
Yes?
然后呢
She seemed to feed it.
她好像在喂它
You.
你
Come here.
过来
I hereby arrest you...
我在此以
on the charge of witchcraft.
涉嫌巫术的罪名逮捕你
Guards.
守卫
Yes, sir.
是的  长官
Aye, sir.
好的  长官